I don't know if this is like a big fiery debate or if I just got thrust into like a very tiny pocket of hostility
But there is right now a raging battle of people
Debating whether or not balding is real kind of that's the statement that started it
That was like the shot heard around the world for this topic. I don't believe in male balding. Why?
First of all if you're a male and you want to go bald that's fine like good for you
However, if you're a male and you don't want to go bald and you're balding anyway
That's where I take issue that opening line right there. I don't believe in male balding actually reached through the fucking phone screen and tickled me
I was a mile in
It goes so hard. I don't believe in male balding shit is a myth. It's like a like a cryptid almost
I've never seen bald man. No such thing. That's a goddamn lie. That's a deep state hooks right there. It's like 5G
I don't know. I just I love that it just slaps. It's not exactly what she's saying
But it's how she lays the foundation the point she's making is that she believes that balding is
Assolved problem and if there's anyone who is bald
Without wanting to be bald. It's due to their laziness
It's fundamentally what she's getting at. She's saying like if you're bald and you choose to be bald
Yippee good for you she says
But if you're balding and you don't want to be balding well, you're just lazy because women in this day and age have to do so much to upkeep their looks and men cannot be bothered to just put some cream on their head or take a little vitamin or get a hair transplant even women are doing more than that
Her point is compared to female beauty standards
Men balding is a significantly easier issue to tackle you can really grab that one by the fucking nipples and solve it with
creams and pills and
Hair transplants and if you are balding and don't want to be well, you're just a gluttonous sloth who is too lazy to fix this problem
And that's kind of the gist of it
I don't think she's super knowledgeable on how expensive like hair transplants are they are not cheap especially in today's day and age
Also being put on medication also not super cheap so like yeah, you can get like the finasteride them in oxydil and like the combo there get it with the fucking two piece and
From everything I understand about it. It seems to work to some degree
It varies person a person obviously because not everyone's just a fucking clone. So
It doesn't work for everybody, but it does work a little bit for some people and for others more so but
It's never like the cure to baldness as I understand it. There's not like a magic pill that like there's no like Phoenix down for your hair
Like you can't
You know chug jug your way to a full head of hair again
Like it is tough and it is very expensive and she's saying women do significantly more than
This but men can't even be bothered to do the bare minimum of stopping the balding with these pills creams and hairs transplants
Again, there's not exactly like it's not curds the cowardly dog where used to skits that handful a shit and can rub it on his head to fix the baldness
Which ultimately led to other problems again a lot of medication does have like side effects and stuff too like it's not exactly the easiest thing
And I recognize that for women there are a lot of things they go through for the sake of like the beauty standards that are put upon them
That are also very difficult
But I don't think those should be celebrated either
And I think there's anything good from putting this pressure on women or men to adhere to the beauty standards that people think they should
More sigma for guys to do beauty products and that includes like hairline stuff guys are like more generally insecure about doing stuff like that
Because they're not really supposed to beauty products. We were sold that that's a girl saying not a guy's thing
I don't know how much of an excuse that is there's not as much pressure on men in society as there is on women to keep their looks
And they just kind of get resigned to the fact that they're going bald versus if you ask any single woman
Something that's happening to their looks that they don't like they will go ahead and fix it
Whether it's like an at home DIY solution to like professional super-exprensive treatment now in the comment section
Everybody was dunking on the guy here saying that he was mansplaining and not listening and that he's
Like not even engaging in the conversation and everyone is on her side about how she's you know out here
Spittening shit in the truth like these are all facts that you speaking about
Balton is not being real and easily solvable. I don't think he did anything wrong
He's right there is a stigma around men using like two pays or wigs because then it's kind of like I'm five six right
The a lot of people joke around like just go get height surgery
Well the people that get height surgery are constantly fucking clowned on they get dunked on more than me at five foot six when I play pick-up basketball
Like you're damned if you do damned if you don't I get made fun of all the time for being short
It is what it is that's the way the cookie crumbles sometimes you got to play with the hand your dealt
My dad is six foot five man stole all the height jeans from our our lineage and then kick the ladder out from under him
Can't do shit about it. I got to live with it
So like I can stay five six and I'm comfortable with it
I make jokes about it, but at the end of the day
I can't fucking change it without going and getting like life-changing surgery that I have me debilitated for like two fucking years as my
My bones reform in my shins
I'm not going to do that
But if I did I would be insulted for being so insecure about my height that I went through those extreme links to change it
And it's the same thing for bald men you'll see this a lot
We're like a bald guy will put on a toupee and it's not like the most optimal one
It's pretty clear he's wearing a toupee people will make fun of him for being so insecure with that
And it's the same thing with other male beauty products that you'll see there is a stigma around it
I don't know why she's pretending that doesn't exist
That's a very common and like really socially acceptable thing to make fun of a guy for
If he's trying to like fix baldness or something and it's not like perfect
You know what I mean? And while I agree with her that these standards for women are higher than that of men
It's not like it doesn't exist for men as I mentioned I'm five foot six
There are innumerable women that want nothing to do romantically with a guy my size
You know petite fun-sized men like me and that's okay
Like it is what it is like I understand that like they're but the point is there is a pressure on men
At least to some degree to a lesser degree than women, but it is there
And what she's reinforcing here is the idea that men have to continuously adhere to an ever increasing pressure on beauty standards
Which is very similar to what women have gone through for a long time
And I think both of these things here are not good like it's not something to encourage and like pump your fist about as like a
celebratory thing. I think it's a bad direction
So the guy's not saying anything wrong here. I don't know why he's getting spit on so much in the comment section
He's he's just saying like hey, you know, there's like a stigma that exists around it
So not every guy's gonna be all gung the hole and like enthusiastic about going and spending thousands upon thousands of dollars on
Creams and pills that aren't super
Efficacious as well as spending thousands and thousands of dollars on a potential hair transplant that might not work super well or might
Might not look all that great like it is it's tricky and it's a tough situation to be in and to her point about female beauty standards
And how much women go through to uphold like the female beauty standards that have been put on them for so many years now
She's not wrong in that perspective, but I don't know why it has to be a battle
I don't know why she needs to now start shaming men for not conforming to male beauty standards that are being put upon them
Like yes, they are significantly more for women, but it's not like men are just allowed to be slabs forever
In fact, I don't know how many of you remember this don tolver
Just took a picture with her had his picture taken with his girlfriend once and the entire internet was insulting him for like
Three full days about how ugly he is and how shameful it is for her to be with him and don tolver
I don't even think is like a really unattractive looking guy like there is still a pressure on men to look good
Because they will also be insulted that is the way the entire culture of like beauty has shifted
Where everyone is expected to uphold like crazy standards, right now of course
I do think it is still more for women
But it's not like it's non-existent for men and I don't think balding is some kind of
Fabrication some kind of made up concept in that it's an easily solvable problem
It's not and I also think that it's very hypocritical if her to take the stance that bald men are lazy
By not going through all of these procedures to try and fix it because women will go through tons of procedures for things
They don't like so like bbl or something or a boob job
But I would also argue that men that are trying to tell women that they need to fix their flat ass or like small titties
Aren't real you're just lazy or equally in the wrong for having that perspective like if this video is completely flipped
Then it was some frat bro sitting there going like yeah bro
I actually don't believe in a cup like honkers of that size
I think are just like actually made made up make believe like just go get a boob job like go take some
Bio tin or something like I'd equally be clouting on him for that perspective too
Like I enforcing those kind of beauty standards and insulting people that don't like conform to it
I think is a bad thing like for women and for men
Girls have a lot of pressure to be valued based off their beauty and guys have a lot of pressure to be valued more on how useful
They are and so guys kind of have an excuse like Jeff Bezos does not have to have hair if he doesn't want to because he has all the money in the world
I know what you mean, but like I wouldn't want to be with Jeff Bezos
He's old what advice ever people that are dating if they're wearing a hat
It might mean they're balding and self-conscious about it
So I would press and see if they're doing anything about that
I love that signing off advice from her right there if you're with a guy who's wearing a hat
This is a clear indicator that there might be some balding under there that he's very self-conscious about so poke the fuck out of it
Make sure to interrogate and if necessary rip that hat right off and reveal the magician secret underneath
There could be a chrome dome and then you need to ask well, what's he doing about it?
I don't know to me that just really rubs me the wrong way because again if you flip this let's say it's a guy saying like if you're with a girl
Who's wearing baggy pants? It might be a clear indicator of a
Not being super cheeked up. There might not be enough cake under there
So make sure to like
Pressor on it like what she doing about that you hitting squats are you getting a bb al any time soon like what what's the regimen to fix this
That's just as bad like I think this whole idea of these beauty standards being forced upon women and men are just getting even more out of control in the
Current climate and it's just a complete race to the bottom
I'm very surprised to see how much support there was behind her statements because I find it to be kind of hypocritical
But again, this is a debate that I don't know how big the topic is I just find it very odd now where
She's coming out here in like shaming dudes for being insecure about balding
But then not fixing it like there are so many
Extinuating factors that could play into that for why they can't fix it like maybe they have tried all the cream savings
Maybe they spent tons and tons of money trying to combat this problem to no avail
Like there are so many things to take into account
If you want to do things to your body that make you happier and more comfortable then go right ahead
But to do it because other people think that it's expected of you
I think it's horrible like some people that are like feeling pressure to get a bucle fat removal procedure or some shit like that because
That's like the beauty trend. It's just not good and it does exist for men to to a lesser degree
I agree with her that women have definitely had more pressure on them when it comes to the beauty standard
But it's not like it is you know
Non-existent when it comes to men as well as evident by this take here that has a lot of support about how like
Men who are bald. They're just lazy. They got to fix it if they're self conscious about baldness and doing nothing about it
They're lazy in fact rip their hat off to double check to make sure they're not bald and insecure and like it's just
I don't I don't love that now. I was pretty surprised that this debate was so split
Well, not even split most people were on her side with the take. It was just surprising as all anyway
I've been yapping about this for a while when really it might just be a full-blown nothing burger of a topic where I got roped into like the
The fucking gravitational pull of the debate like the actual epicenter no idea
But I found it to be interesting nonetheless. That's about it. See ya